{
  "extraDescription": "second operand is never greater than first operand",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "2"
    }
  ]
}
